{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Louise__film_",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance created the film Louise.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8114063143730164,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6617031693458557,
            "question": "Who directed the film Louise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6116307973861694,
            "question": "Was Abel Gance a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5797756314277649,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Abel Gance."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5767014026641846,
            "question": "What year was the film Louise released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102251172065735,
            "question": "What genre is the film Louise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48960208892822266,
            "question": "What was innovative about Abel Gance's filmmaking style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47162941098213196,
            "question": "Are there any other notable films directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36455509066581726,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the plot of Louise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3136845827102661,
            "question": "Who are some actors who appeared in Louise?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance created the film Louise.",
            "html": "yago_4188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the plot of Louise?",
            "html": "yago_4188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable films directed by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was innovative about Abel Gance's filmmaking style?",
            "html": "yago_4188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4188_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Abel Gance directed the film \"Louise,\" which supports the statement that Abel Gance created the film Louise."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}